http://www.archaeologychannel.org/privacy-policy

The Archaeology Channel
Exploring the human cultural heritage through streaming media
SEARCH
Go
Toggle navigation
MENU
HomeVideoVideo GuideListSummaryMapStrata: Portraits of HumanityVideo News from TACVideo InterviewsVideo CommentariesKentucky VideosMaking Archaeology Public ProjectAudioAudio News from ArchaeologicaAudio InterviewsAudio CommentariesIndigenous Storytelling: Kalapuya Creation StoryThe Human ExperienceWisdom of the EldersIndiana Jones: Myth, Reality and 21st Century ArchaeologyEventsTAC International Film Festival2021 FestivalPast FestivalsTAC Conference on Cultural Heritage MediaLegacyQuest Film FestivalArchaeologyFest Film SeriesTAC Festival On the RoadFilm Festivals WorldwideTAC ToursResourcesGoods & ServicesTeacher ResourcesNews & BlogsWeb LinksFilm ProductionGet HelpOur FilmsStoreParticipateMembershipJoin/RenewAboutMember OrganizationsUnderwritingVolunteerShow/Distribute Your WorkAboutOur OrganizationOfficers and StaffLogo and WebsiteContactDonate!
Welcome to our Privacy Policy.
Your privacy is critically important to us.
The location of Archaeological Legacy Institute is:
Archaeological Legacy Institute4147 E. Amazon Dr.Eugene, ORUnited State of America541-345-5538
It is Archaeological Legacy Institute’s (hereinafter, “ALI”) policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.archaeologychannel.org/ (hereinafter, "us," "we," or "https://www.archaeologychannel.org/"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through our website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the terms and conditions posted on our website, sets forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our website. Depending on your activities when visiting our website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, ALI collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ALI's purpose in collecting non-personally-identifying information is to understand better how ALI's visitors use its website. From time to time, ALI may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
ALI also collects potentially personally identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged-in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.archaeologychannel.org/ blog posts. ALI discloses logged-in user and commenter IP addresses only under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally Identifying Information
Certain visitors to ALI's websites choose to interact with ALI in ways that require ALI to gather personally identifying information. The amount and type of information that ALI gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for our newsletter at https://www.archaeologychannel.org/ to provide their name and email address.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Advertisements
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks, among other things, to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ALI and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Links To External Sites
Our service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Protection of Certain Personally Identifying Information
ALI discloses potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on ALI's behalf or to provide services available at ALI's website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By using ALI's website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. ALI will not rent or sell potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, ALI discloses potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when ALI believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ALI, third parties or the public at large.
If you are a registered user of https://www.archaeologychannel.org/ and have supplied your email address, ALI may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback or just keep you up to date with what's going on with ALI and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. ALI takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information.
Aggregated Statistics
ALI may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. ALI may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, ALI does not disclose your personally identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, ALI uses "cookies," similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer. A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ALI uses cookies to help ALI identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.archaeologychannel.org/ and their website access preferences. ALI visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ALI's websites, with the drawback that certain features of ALI's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to ALI's use of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with ALI by purchasing ALI's services or products are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, ALI collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with ALI. ALI does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, ALI may change its Privacy Policy from time to time and in ALI's sole discretion. ALI encourages visitors to check this page frequently for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
© 2020 Archaeological Legacy Institute, Non-Profit
Home  |  About  |  Contact  |  Volunteer  |  Privacy Policy
Youtube
FeedBurner Feed
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
LinkedIn Group
